It's Saturday night fever every night.
54 is a drama, music film directed by Mark Christopher.
When the mastermind behind New York's infamous Studio 54 disco plucks young Shane from the sea of faces clamoring to get inside his club, he not only
gets his foot in the door, but lands a coveted job behind the bar — and a front-row ticket to the most legendary party on the planet!
Shane O'Shea, played by Ryan Phillippe.
Steve Rubell, played by Mike Myers.
Anita, played by Salma Hayek Pinault.
Greg Randazzo, played by Breckin Meyer.
Julie Black, played by Neve Campbell.
Billie Auster, played by Sela Ward.
54 is a 1998 American drama film written and directed by Mark Christopher.
Starring Ryan Phillippe, Salma Hayek, Neve Campbell, and Mike Myers, the film focuses on the rise and fall
of Studio 54, a famous nightclub in New York City during the late 1970s and early 1980s.
Prior to its release in the United States on August 28, 1998, by Miramax Films, the film was
extensively reshot and recut; it ultimately opened to poor critical reaction and box office.
In 2008, a bootleg version of the director's cut was screened at
Outfest, leading to interest for its release.
In 2015, Christopher and Miramax premiered a new edit of the film at the 65th Berlin International Film
Festival, with 45 minutes of original material restored and 30 minutes of studio re-shoots removed.
The film explores themes of new york city, love triangle, 1970s, fbi, nightclub.
The tone is emotional.